Want to take a walk with me?
...continue to protest the presence
of a convicted sex offender
in their neighborhood.
Michelle Betler reports.
Thanks, Rick. I'm standing here
on Woodward Court,
the quiet residential
street
that has become
the focus of controversy
ever since 48-year-old
Ronald James McGorvey returned here
after serving a two-year
prison sentence
for indecent exposure
to a minor.
In the past few days
an organization
known as the Committee
of Concerned Parents
began distributing these notices
throughout the community
warning neighbors
of what they call a quote,
"Dangerous predator
in our midst."
I don't really like having
him that close to my family.
I think it's outrageous.
This block has too many children
for a sex offender to, uh, be
moving in the neighborhood.
I-- I don't think
it's a good idea.
Makes me very nervous.
Makes me a little enraged.
Um, I'd have a problem
if I see him on the street.
It's like having an
alcoholic work in a bar.
They don't mix.
They shouldn't be together.
The conditions of his parole
expressly forbid McGorvey
to be within 100 yards
of any playground,
school or recreation area
where children normally gather.
These conditions seem
to be of little comfort
to the many parents whose
children play and go to school
in this formerly
tranquil community,
and who in the coming days and weeks
will be hoping for the best
but preparing for the worst.
Rick, back to you.
My husband and I had an
actual spiritual experience.
We did this intense
spa treatment--
- Oh, come on.
- No, listen to me.
It was on our vacation in Cabo
and there were eight other couples
and this Mayan woman.
A goddess,
just a goddess.
- She had--
- She's due in September.
She thinks she's gonna
take three months off,
then it's Christmas, then she'll be back
to work the first of the year.
Please.
Six months from now she'll be right here
on this bench with us.
My friend Beth said
that the way she did it
was to just take him with her every time
she went to the bathroom.
- I find that strange.
- Yeah, that's what I said to Beth.
It's Oedipal.
What's the rush?
Although I will say, when I was trying
to potty-train Christian,
I opened the diaper
and it was huge!
Like a grown man.
Smiling politely to mask a
familiar feeling of desperation
Sarah reminded herself to think
like an anthropologist.
She was a researcher studying the
behavior of typical suburban women.
They weren't organic?
She was not a typical
suburban woman herself.
Troy, stop that!
Paul and I were having
sex the other night
and I drifted off
right in the middle of it.
It happens.
Yeah, I guess.
But when I woke up and apologized
he said he hadn't
even noticed.
You know what
you should do?
Set aside a specific
block of time for it.
That's what Louis and I do--
every Tuesday night at 9:00.
"Whether you want to or not"
Sarah thought,
her eyes straying over
to the play area.
Even at such a tiny
playground as this
Lucy didn't interact much
with the other children.
Sarah didn't really know why
they even bothered coming here,
except that she'd
probably go crazy
trapped in the house
all day
with this unknowable
little person.
Morning snack time
was 10:30 on the dot...
Snack time!
...a regimen established
and maintained by Mary Ann,
who believed that rigid
adherence to a timetable
was not only the key
to a healthy marriage,
but to effective
parenting as well.
- I'll take this one!
- I want that one!
- Can I do it?
- Yeah. Ready?
Mommy...
where's my snack?
I'm sorry, honey,
Mommy can't find it.
- I forgot the rice cakes.
- Poor thing.
- I'm sure it's in here somewhere.
- Second time this week.
Well, who's going to keep
track of everything?
- Bad mommy. Bad mommy.
- Just calm down, please.
No calm down!
I want my snack!
All right, you know what?
It's--
it's just not here, okay?
See for yourself.
Wait!
Troy, honey,
give Lucy your goldfish.
No!
Troy Jonathan,
give me those goldfish!
But, Mama, they're mine.
No back talk.
You can share with your sister.
Troy has goldfish for you.
Go sit down.
That's much more than 10.
- That's great.
- Look how big I made my lawn.
Thank you, Mary Ann,
you're a life saver.
It's nothing.
I just hate to see her suffer like that.
Maybe you should make
a checklist and tape it to the door
so it's the last thing you
see before leaving the house.
That's what I do.
Yeah, thank you. That's-- that's
a really helpful suggestion.
You're welcome.
Drink your juice.
Are you the plane again?
Look.
Now you have to act like me.
The prom king.
Oh my God,
he's back.
Sarah followed
the other women's gazes
over to the entrance
of the playground,
eager to finally get a glimpse
of the prom king,
the handsome and mysterious
young father
who had been a regular
at the Walker Street playground
for several weeks
this past spring
before abruptly
dropping out of sight.
I don't need a rest.
I need an airplane ride.
His departure had left a gaping
hole in the emotional lives
of Cheryl, Theresa
and Mary Ann.
Barely a day went by without one
of them speculating wistfully
about the reason for his absence
and the likelihood of his return.
Here I come.
There's no room for two of us, diesel.
You've done it again.
I hate steam engines.
When I come back I will
pinch you with my pinchers.
Yeah?
Well, when I come back
I'm gonna ram you
with my rammer.
- Ready?
- No, you won't.
Every time you win,
diesel!
I know.
- Hello!
- Mommy's home.
The jester's cap was something
that truly disturbed Brad.
All day long the boy ate,
played and napped in it.
But the moment his mother stepped in
the house he had no more use for it.
As if the entire day
up to that point
had been a pointless
and somewhat useless charade.
You got some sun
today, didn't you?
Did Daddy forget
the sunscreen again?
What are you doing?
That's his full name.
What's your favorite thing about him?
Um...
I like to come over
to his house.
Hmm.
I think I'm gonna finally break down
and get a cellphone.
- Really?
- Mmm.
Why?
I have no way of reaching you
when I'm out with Aaron.
You're done,
right?
You've got one.
Don't you think it's
strange that I don't?
Yeah, I do.
You just never wanted one before.
Yeah, I know.
There's a family plan.
We can talk for free.
Okay.
Let's just see where we are
at the end of the month.
Yeah?
Are your hands okay?
As was her custom each week
night after dinner,
the boy's mother sent Brad
down to the municipal library
to study for the bar exam.
But he never quite made it through
the door of the building.
Brad had been watching
the skateboarders for weeks now,
sometimes for as long
as an hour at a stretch.
But he never received the slightest
acknowledgement from any of them.
He'd been the same age as these
boys when his mother died.
- You do that!
- No way!
- Nice.
- Hey, that was nice, dude!
"I must have been like this,"
Brad sometimes thought.
"I must have been
one of them."
Awful.
He should be castrated.
Quick and clean,
just chop it off.
Then you wouldn't have to worry
about notifying the neighbors.
You know what else
you should do?
Nail his penis above the entrance
to the elementary school.
You know, as a warning
to other perverts.
You think
this is funny?
I just can't believe you want to
castrate a man for indecent exposure.
My brother used
to expose himself when--
when we were teenagers.
He'd do it in my bedroom,
he'd do it in the dining room,
he'd do it in the back seat of a car.
He'd always figure out a way to do it so
that nobody could see him except me.
Didn't you
tell anyone?
No, I didn't want
to get him in trouble.
Maybe he should
be castrated.
It's not the same thing.
He wasn't doing it to strangers.
Oh my God, there he is.
After all this time,
two days in a row.
Where's the fire?
Maybe he needed a vacation.
From what?
From being
the prom king.
It's a dirty job,
but someone's gotta do it.
- Close it?
- Close it.
Close the gate.
There you go.
- It's open.
- It's all right.
- Somebody else will close it.
- Are we practicing?
Are we playing
up on the swings?
Swing time!
What's he do for a living?
We've never actually
spoken to him.
Really?
We don't even
know his name.
I thought you guys said
he was a regular here.
- It was awkward.
- He made us nervous.
You had to think about what you
were gonna wear in the morning.
You know, put on makeup.
It was exhausting.
Mommy, push me!
Okay.
I'll be right there.
Wait!
Five bucks if you get
his phone number.
How old is she?
Lucy,
tell the nice boy
how old you are.
I'm three.
My grandma
lives in New Jersey.
She doesn't have
a swim pool.
Do you like to swim?
I don't like sharks.
They eat you up.
Don't listen to him.
We go to the town pool
almost every day.
- I'm Brad, by the way.
- Sarah.
You guys come
here a lot?
No, just the last
few weeks.
I usually go to the one
over on Harris,
with the big wood things,
you know, and the slide across.
Yeah, we actually rent a house
right around the corner
from there on Ashforth.
That ice cream truck never leaves.
Such a nightmare.
Yeah, tell me about it.
You know, you're the first person
here who's ever talked to me.
You make 'em nervous.
Oh, right.
I guess they don't see too many fathers
here during the weekdays.
You don't have to be polite.
Go ahead and ask.
What?
You know, what the person who wears the
pants in the family does for a living.
Oh. All right,
what does your wife do?
- She makes documentaries.
- Oh, wow.
- Like Michael Moore?
- Uh, like PBS.
Oh.
Well, I think it's
admirable you're here.
There's no reason fathers
can't be primary caregivers.
I finished law school
two years ago,
but I can't seem to pass the bar exam.
Failed it twice now.
Maybe you just don't
want to be a lawyer.
I'll take the test
one more time.
If I mess up now
I'll just have to find something else
to do with my life.
- Right, buddy?
- Right.
Sarah was shocked by how Brad
delivered this confession,
with no apparent sense of being in the
least bit embarrassed by his failure.
Most men weren't like this.
Her husband Richard
certainly wasn't.
She wondered if Brad was
always this forthcoming.
If anything,
he seemed a little lonely,
all too ready to open his heart at
the slightest sign of interest,
like a lot of young
mothers she knew.
I couldn't help noticing
your stroller.
Do you have
another child?
No, just Aaron.
Got that at a yard sale.
Extra seat comes in handy
for the bear, though.
Lucy refuses to go
in a stroller or a car seat.
We have to walk everywhere. It takes us
half an hour to go three blocks,
unless I carry her.
- Daddy, I'm finished.
- Are you sure? We just got here.
I'm finished right now.
Okay. All right,
here we go.
Ready?
One, two, three.
- Oops.
- Oh, hold on for a second.
- There, thank you.
- Are you okay?
No problem.
It was then while watching Brad
kneel down at his son's feet
that Sarah found herself gripped by
an unexpected pang of sadness.
"Don't go," she thought.
"Don't leave me here
with the others."
- It was nice talking to you.
- Same here.
Wait! Um...
Come here. Just...
come here.
You see those women
over there?
Just, yeah, don't--
don't look.
You know what
they call you?
What?
The prom king.
Oh God, really?
Yeah, they mean it
as a compliment.
You're a big character
in their fantasy lives.
Wow.
Um, so one of them bet me $5
I couldn't get your phone number.
Five bucks, huh?
Yeah.
Could we split
it 50-50?
It could be
arranged.
It doesn't have to be
your real number.
Oh, well, you know, in that case, sure.
You got a pen?
Great. Oh shit, no I--
um, no I don't.
- Uh...
- Well...
No wait, just--
wait.
You know what'd
really be funny?
If you gave me a hug.
- You think?
- Yeah.
- All right, come here.
Oh my God.
Do you want to really
freak them out?
Yeah.
Who's gonna talk in there?
- Oh my God!
- Troy!
- Lucy!
- Isabelle!
Isabelle! Come here, Isabelle.
Okay, we have to go.
- Isabelle!
- Troy!
- I think that worked.
- Yeah, I think so.
- Um, well, it was nice meeting you.
- Yeah.
It's okay, yeah.
We're gonna go.
- It's all right.
- Lucy?
We're gonna go home.
Okay, here we go,
good girl.
Good girl.
I'm sure your daughter
found that very educational.
His name is Brad.
He's a lawyer
and he's really very nice.
For the past few days
Sarah hadn't been able
to concentrate on anything
but the prom king
and the curious thing
that had happened
between them
on the playground.
She didn't feel
shame or guilt,
only a sense of profound
disorientation,
as if she had been
kidnapped by aliens
then released unharmed
a few hours later.
As he had so often
in recent days,
Brad mentally reenacted
the kiss by the swing set.
He still couldn't believe
it had really happened.
And with all those women
and children watching.
Troy! Troy!
Aaron had been particularly
curious about what he'd seen.
Why you hugging
that lady?
Well, that's what
I'm trying to show you with Bozo.
Sometimes it's a game that adults play
to show that they're friends.
You say, "Hi,
I'm your friend."
Aaron was skeptical.
They returned to the playground
the following morning,
but no one was there.
Sarah hadn't shown up
at the town pool either,
though Brad remembered telling
her that he and Aaron
could be found there
most afternoons.
It didn't seem to matter
that Sarah wasn't his type,
wasn't even that pretty--
at least not compared to Kathy,
who had long legs
and lustrous hair
and perfect breasts.
Sarah was short, boyish,
and had eyebrows that were thicker
than Brad thought necessary.
But even so, she'd walked
into his arms that day
as if she were fulfilling
a secret wish
he hadn't remembered
making.
Hey, pervert!
Yeah, you,
you pervert!
You like little
boys, do you?
- Larry?
- Yes, it's fucking Larry!
Jesus, man, don't
even joke about that.
What are you doing?
Are you busy?
Uh, actually I'm
supposed to be studying.
Taking the bar exam
next month.
I thought you
did that last year.
Yeah.
See how well I did?
I got a better idea.
Get in.
Come on. Come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on.
Do you mind holding these?
Try to keep them nice.
Oh, uh...
are you, uh, part
of the committee?
I am the committee.
Wow.
That's-- that's
quite a commitment.
Yeah.
Aren't you full time
on the force already?
Yeah, I'm-- I'm taking
a little time off.
You know what
they should do to this bastard?
Just castrate him.
You know, pfft!
Get it over with,
right?
Yeah.
You look good.
You've been, uh,
working out?
Uh, just push-ups,
crunches...
a little light running.
The guys are
gonna love this.
What guys?
Wow, this is something.
Yeah, it's pretty,
but doesn't have a lot of give.
It's like
playing on cement.
Hey, hold on
a second.
Duane, I've really gotta talk
to you about the committee.
I mean, it would mean a lot to have
your support on this thing.
I told you already, Larry, none of us
are gonna get involved in that shit.
We're here to play ball. If that's your
thing, fine, but leave us out of it.
Okay okay, fine.
I get it, I get it, I get it. Guys!
Bring it in!
Come on, come on,
hustle up!
I want you all to meet
our new quarterback.
- Quarterback?
- Guy better not be a pussy.
He played in college.
Uh, I'm a little
behind the curve.
Who are you guys?
- We're the Guardians!
- We're cops.
Welcome to the Tri-County
touch football night league.
Let's just work on some
simple pass patterns.
Brad waited for his
good sense to kick in.
There were lots of excuses
available to him.
But it felt so good to be standing here
beneath the bright lights.
And he was filled
with a feeling similar to the one
he'd had right
before kissing Sarah,
like his world had
cracked open
to reveal a thrilling
new possibility.
Okay, just let me
warm up a little.
All right! Let's go!
Set, hut!
What the fuck?
That's a late hit!
This ain't
Pop Warner, ace.
You fucking faggot.
You call yourself a quarterback?
Oh, this isn't me.
What are you doing?
What is that?
What's that for?
I want the scumbag
to know I'm keeping an eye on him.
Oh, shit.
Oh, uh...
I don't think we want
to be here, Larry.
It's not a question
of want.
Joanie thinks I'm
obsessed with this creep.
She thinks if I had a job, I wouldn't
be driving past his house
five, six times a day.
But you know what?
I kinda think
this is my job.
There's a roll of duct tape
in the glove compartment.
Would you grab it for me?
Honey?
Hi!
Where were you?
Oh my God.
What happened?
I-- I-- I joined
this group.
The Committee
for Concerned Parents.
We're distributing flyers about
that creep on Woodward Court.
These guys play a little
touch football after.
This late?
Uh, it's a night league.
So it's gonna be
a regular thing?
No no no no,
just once a week,
after I'm done
studying at the library.
Is that okay?
Uh, who are the guys?
You remember
Larry Hedges?
The guy from the Sprinkler
Park with the twins?
It's his organization.
I thought you
didn't like him.
He's okay.
This committee makes a
lot of sense. I mean it's--
it's pretty scary having
a weirdo like that
living right
by the playground.
Mmm.
I know.
I hate to even
think about it.
Guess you'd better
take a shower.
Brad showered quickly,
sensing a rare opportunity
to have sex with his wife.
"This is just what I need,"
he thought.
"Something to take
my mind off that kiss."
Please don't.
Come on, Kathy, we've
been through this before.
He needs to start
sleeping by himself.
I know.
He looks so comfy.
Well, he'll be just
as comfy in his own bed.
I just miss
him so much.
I'm getting a little tired waking up
with his foot in my face.
It's a perfect foot.
Look at him.
Just look at him.
He's a handsome devil.
Mmm, he's perfect.
Good night.
Number 2 Hillcrest
was an impressive
piece of real estate.
Even so,
Sarah was ambivalent
about the house
she occupied.
She wasn't involved
with its purchase or design.
The place was a hand-me-down of sorts
from Richard's mother.
And the furnishings
were leftovers from his first marriage.
By the time
Sarah arrived here
Richard wasn't all that
interested in redecorating.
And so she decided
to leave it as it was,
with the exception of a single room
that she staked out for her own
and gradually began
to populate it
with the remnants
of her former self.
From the moment
Lucy was born
Sarah had refused to hire
someone for child care.
Read me a story?
In a minute,
okay?
- Can I sit on your lap?
- I said in a minute!
Go finish your
program, go.
She wasn't exactly sure
why she had taken this stance.
The truth was she spent
most afternoons marking time,
waiting desperately for the moment
when her husband returned from work
and she could finally
have a moment to herself.
But even this was not
something she could rely on.
You're ready to roll?
Could you wait
a few minutes?
I'm sorry, Richard's barricaded
in the upstairs office
- finishing some stuff for work.
- No problem.
I've got a little surprise
for someone anyway.
She's a terror at night.
I couldn't get her to nap again.
- Oh, the poor thing.
- Poor mom is more like it.
Hello.
Is there a cute little
girl in the house?
Oh, my goodness!
What--
what have I found?
- A beanie.
- Oh, a beanie.
Jean, you didn't
need to to that.
Oh, this little dog needed
a girl to take care of him.
And I know a little girl
who needed a dog.
Let me see.
Sarah was beginning
to get angry.
Her evening fitness walk
was the one thing
she looked forward to all day,
and Richard knew this.
But if there was one thing
life had taught Richard,
it was that it was
ridiculous
to be at war
with your own desires.
He could easily imagine what people
would say if they could see him now--
Exactly the same thing they'd
say if someone had told them
that Ray from next door
was a transvestite,
or that Ted from work
had anonymous gay sex
at highway rest stops.
"But we want what we want,"
Richard thought,
"and there's not much
we can do about it."
He had stumbled
on the site 11 months ago
while doing research
for a consulting firm.
His office door
was wide open.
But he clicked
on the link anyway.
He was deeply engrossed
in his discovery
when Ted knocked
on his door.
I'm taking lunch orders.
You want something?
Casually, but with great haste
Richard banished Slutty Kay
from his screen...
Uh, yeah, I'll have
a chicken Caesar.
...and reentered the flow
of an ordinary day.
It wasn't until
several months later
that Richard gave the slightest thought
to the site he had stumbled upon.
Do you need me
for anything else?
Uh, no no, you
can head home.
I'm just gonna catch up
on some e-mail.
Well, don't stay too late.
Your dinner will get cold.
Lately Slutty Kay
had become a problem.
He thought about her
far too often,
and spent hours studying
the thousands of photographs
available to him.
Some of Kay's practices
struck him as bizarre,
even off-putting.
She had a thing
about kitchen utensils,
spatulas, and dressing up
like a little girl
and playing with balloons.
But who was
Richard to judge?
Oh, that's it.
Though as close as Richard
sometimes felt to Slutty Kay,
as much as he believed
that he knew her,
he could never get past
the uncomfortable fact
that she existed for him
solely as a digital image.
The panties were an attempt
to solve this problem.
Maybe a sniff or two
would hurry things along,
so he could get back
downstairs to his real life,
where his wife
was waiting for him
her impatience increasing
by the minute.
What are you doing?
Are you almost finished there? 'Cause
I'd really like to go for my walk?
- You could have knocked.
- I did!
We need to talk.
You're awfully quiet
this evening.
- Everything okay?
- What?
Yeah.
You'll have to walk
without me tomorrow night.
I've got a book
group meeting.
Okay.
You're sure everything's
all right?
Yeah, sorry.
I guess I'm just
a little tired.
So what are
you reading?
"Crime and
Punishment."
Wow. That's pretty
highbrow for a book group.
Well, we have some
very stimulating discussions.
You should come next month.
We're doing "Madame Bovary."
You could be
my little sister.
Little sister?
We're trying to get younger
women involved.
We call them
our little sisters.
I don't know, Jean.
I read "Madame Bovary"
in grad school.
It's a pretty
misogynist text.
Well, that's an
interesting perspective.
- You should come.
- Let me think about it.
Oh, would you
excuse me, Jean?
Someone's at my door.
I'll call you, okay?
Hi!
Wow, God,
this is a surprise.
I haven't seen
you since--
I-- I hope you don't mind. Your husband
said you'd be back any minute.
Oh, no,
not at all.
It's good
to see you.
God, um, can I get you
some tea or something?
I can only stay a minute.
I just came to warn you.
- You know that guy, the pervert?
- Uh-huh.
He's been riding his
bike near the playground
- checking out the kids.
- Oh, God.
Oh, God,
do the police know?
Nothing they can do.
He's not breaking any laws.
I guess they're just waiting
for him to kill someone.
I just thought
you should know.
Thanks, that's
nice of you.
Let me get
you some tea.
I'm sorry.
I-- I don't think it's a good idea.
I didn't mean
to kiss him.
I don't even know
how it happened.
I'd better go.
Mike's gonna worry.
You wanna talk?
I'm tired.
Hello.
Hey.
No, he's still
sleeping.
Yeah, I'm, uh, I'm going
through it right now.
No, I guess I
don't need them.
Okay.
All right, bye.
H-hi.
H-hello?
Yes, I'd like
to place an order.
Pierce, Sarah,
Mrs.
Um...
it's the red bathing suit
on page 29.
The hide-your-tummy
halter neck.
Uh, I'm size...
10, eight?
I mean, I think.
E-eight.
You want to go
in the pool?
You do?
One, two.
Daddy, can I go
in the pool now?
In a minute, okay?
Okay.
There you go.
Mommy, I have
to go pee-pee.
Just go in the pool.
Huh-uh, I want
to go to the bathroom.
Really?
Okay, come on.
Okay, ready?
There.
Swing down.
Hey, I'm drumming it.
Oh.
Wow.
- It's you.
- Yeah, hey.
- Hi!
- Okay.
I hope you don't mind.
Lucy has sensitive skin.
She's better off
in the shade.
Oh no,
not at all.
It's nice
to see you again.
Yeah, you too.
I'm sorry,
would you get my back?
Um...
okay, sure.
Thanks.
Right.
# Who is knocking
on the door? #
- Thanks a lot.
- # Knocking on the door #
# Knocking on the door #
- # Who is knocking on the door? #
- It's okay, just...
# A way, hey hey. #
Lucy, say hi to the little boy
from the playground.
Hi.
You remember him?
The pool became a ritual.
I was trying to think.
I just didn't know the way.
- Oh oh, okay.
- I'm here, I'm here.
We have the creature
and we have flower.
Right.
Day after day they sat
together in the shade
getting to know
each other.
This needs mustard.
- Mustard?
- Yeah.
Having little choice
in the matter,
Aaron and Lucy formed
a fragile friendship.
Aw, that's perfect.
Sometimes Brad and Sarah
traded offspring.
Mama said, "What Papa
told you was right.
It's not a good idea
to talk to strangers."
It was the most fun
Sarah had had in years.
But there was always
that longing to touch,
to be touched by Brad.
And, as badly as
she wanted this,
she wanted just as badly
to hold on to the innocent public life
they'd made for themselves
out in the open.
So she accepted
the trade--
the melancholy
handshake at 4:00
in exchange for this
little patch of grass,
some sunscreen
and companionship.
One more happy day
at the pool.
Okay, no pasta
for dinner, okay?
We eat way too much
pasta around here.
I thought you
liked my pasta.
No, I do.
That's the problem.
Pretty soon I can sell advertising
space on my ass.
No, that's okay.
I've got to go.
I've got
a 9:00 at Taps.
I thought you were
already editing.
Yeah, so did I.
It was just--
there's something in this
family's story that really got to me.
The father was...
K-I-L-L-E-D
in a, um,
mortar attack,
and, um, left behind
a little boy.
I was talking to the mother the other
day on the phone,
and she was saying she didn't know what
she was going to do next Christmas.
Jeez, I bet.
No, it wasn't like that.
It was more...
she was wondering, should she keep
this tradition with her son
that began with
the boy's father.
And she was saying
he had this knack
for requesting
odd Christmas gifts--
scuba gear one year
and rappelling gear
the next.
She said he wasn't
afraid to try anything.
Trying new things
made him feel...
more alive.
I've got to go.
See you later.
Patch one of your best
and then we'll patch both of them.
Okay?
Hey, I got something.
Hot enough for you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's so humid.
I've got football
practice tonight.
Be like playing
in a sauna.
Watch out for
that Italian guy.
What's his name?
Corrente?
Yeah.
Remember what
happened to your knee last week?
You should be
careful, Brad.
I'll be careful.
Promise?
Yeah.
Yeah, I promise.
Weatherman said
scattered showers.
I don't see
Mom, could I please
have some money for a snack?
No, sweetheart.
You guys just had a snack. No.
Oh, okay.
All they want is sugar.
Constantly.
Oh, no.
It's him.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh my God,
it's him.
He's in the pool.
Oh my God!
Jacob, get out
of the pool now!
Oh my God.
That's him.
- Get away from that man.
- Why is everybody running to the pool?
Brooke?
Jake?
Dale, you'd better
get over here.
Get out of the pool!
Where's your sister?
Why'd we have to get out, Mom?
I'm scared.
- What did he do?
- What's going on?
I'm scared.
Um, why the
police is here?
Um, there's a man over there who
doesn't have a ticket to get in,
so they're asking
him to go home.
Mr. McGorvey.
It'd be wise for you to get
out of the pool at this time.
Did that man
go near you?
You're sure he
didn't touch you?
Step out of
the pool, sir.
I was only trying
to cool off.
All right,
let's go.
You can go back in the pool.
Bear with us, please. You
know what that sounds means.
Let's go. Out of the pool.
We're closing her up. Let's go.
Exit the pool and vacate
the grounds immediately.
Okay, I'll see
you tomorrow.
You're going to carry her?
Come on, put her in the stroller.
No, she won't do the stroller.
- Really?
- No, she will not do this.
Lucy, would you like to go
in the stroller?
Can I interest you in a stroller?
It appears she'd like a stroller.
It's out of
your way.
No, it's fine.
You don't mind, do you, Aaron?
Run!
You'd better come inside.
You can't walk home in this.
Oh!
- You can put him down in Lucy's room.
- Okay.
This is amazing.
She never naps.
Well, he'll be
out for the next two hours.
We'll have to get him out
of that nightgown, though,
before he wakes up
or he'll never forgive me.
Nice place.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
Well, Richard does
all right for himself.
What's he do, again?
Lies. Um, please have a seat.
Make yourself comfortable.
Better not,
I might ruin your furniture.
I'll put these things in the dryer
and get us some towels.
Okay.
Oh, God!
Do you feel bad
about this?
No, I don't.
I do.
I feel really bad.
Okay.
Son?
Be well.
May knew it wasn't natural
for a grown man
to be living with his mother.
No hobbies,
no diversions.
It was like he was
still in prison.
What he needed
was a girlfriend,
and May intended to
help him find one.
There are four whole columns
of lonely women here,
and only a handful of men.
The odds are on our side.
Why wouldn't one of
these women want
to meet a nice
person like you?
I'm not
a nice person.
You did a bad thing.
But that doesn't mean
you're a bad person.
I have a psychosexual
disorder.
You're better now.
They wouldn't have let
you out if you weren't.
They let me out
because they had to.
Well, maybe
if you found
a girlfriend closer
to your own age
you wouldn't have
the bad urges so often.
I don't want a girlfriend
my own age, Mommy.
I wish I did.
What are you going
to do when I'm gone?
Who's going to
take care of you?
What's the matter,
Mommy?
Are you sick
or something?
I'm an old woman.
I'm not going to live forever,
Who's going to cook
for you?
Who's going
to wash the dishes?
I can wash
the dishes,
You've never washed
a dish in your life.
I could do it if I had to.
I'm not a retard.
No, you're not.
You're a miracle,
Ronnie.
We're all miracles.
You know why?
Because as humans,
everyday we go
about our business,
and all that time
we know, we all know
that the things
we love,
the people we love...
at any time, it can
all be taken away.
We live knowing that
and we keep
going anyway.
Animals don't do that.
Now I'm not asking you
to get married, Ronnie.
I'm just saying put an ad in the paper,
see what happens.
Fine. I'll do it if
it will make you happy.
But just one date.
All right?
You have a nice smile,
why don't we start with that?
What else?
You always eat what I put in front
of you. You never complain.
What else?
You're trying to
get back in shape.
You exercise.
Wait right there,
young man.
If you're going out
for some exercise,
you can post this now.
Hmm.
Mmm.
Come on.
Let's do it again.
All right.
God, it's hot
as hell up here.
What's wrong with
the laundry room?
No mattress.
Come on.
Lie down.
You're nervous,
aren't you?
What?
What do you mean?
The game.
Don't worry.
You'll be great tonight.
I don't know.
I haven't played in 10 years.
It used to be
my whole life.
Then when I stopped,
I just...
stopped. I didn't
even miss it.
Now that I'm playing
again, I...
feel I--
I don't know.
You feel alive.
Yeah.
That's good.
That's how you're
supposed to feel.
You're right.
I guess it's just
been awhile.
Yeah.
Shake.
- Call it.
- Heads.
Heads it is.
Ready?
- Hello?
- Hi, Mom. Did I wake you?
Oh, no honey.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You don't
sound fine.
No, there's nothing wrong.
I just wanted to say hi.
Well, hi.
Hi.
So how's my
little guy?
He's great.
He's sleeping right here next to me.
He's such
a cutie.
So where's Brad?
Brad's out.
Oh, I'm surprised
the library stays open this late.
Well, he's not
at the library.
He's playing football
with some buddies.
Oh, honey. Do you remember when
your father took up golf?
He's not
like dad.
Honey, they're
all the same.
Well, he's not.
You work so hard.
Now listen...
I could keep an eye
on the boys when you're at work;
make sure they're
staying out of trouble.
- Do you want me to come up for a visit?
- No no, Mom, don't come.
Well, honey, I worry
about you kids.
Now what are you going to do if he
fails the test again?
He's not going
to fail the test.
Oh, honey,
that's what you said last time.
Now how are you
doing for money?
We're fine.
I'm going to send you a little
extra this month.
- Mom...
- Honey, it's no burden.
- Mom... Mom, please.
- I'm happy to help.
Aw, shit.
Although the Guardians
lost by 26 points,
Brad felt oddly exhilarated in the bar
after the game.
He could feel a new respect
in the way the cops looked at him.
- What you drinking, buddy?
- He wasn't on probation anymore.
He was a member
of the team.
Ice and Advil.
If all else fails, you can always see
the team physician,
Dr. Daniels.
All his friends call him Jack.
- To the good doctor.
- Hear, hear.
- Larry? Here, you go Larry.
- Oh, thanks.
Let me just
grab a chair.
Oh, we just gave you a shot.
We just gave you a shot.
I had no business being
on that field tonight.
I let you down.
I let the whole
team down.
I'm slow and
I'm fat.
I let that guy
piss all over me.
Come on. That guy was offsides
the whole night.
Joanie left me.
Took the kids and went
to her mother's.
Jesus, Larry,
that's a tough break.
Oh, I deserved it.
Me and my big mouth.
I called her
a fucking whore,
right in front
of the kids.
Why did you do that?
Huh,
I don't know.
I was in a bad mood
or something.
Now I'm fucked.
Hey, did you hear
about the pervert?
He went swimming
at the town pool.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Who told you that?
- Nobody. I saw it myself.
- The town pool?
- Yeah, during the heatwave.
- Yep.
Th-that place is
crawling with kids.
I mean, my boys
go there.
Yeah, well, you know what,
it was just that one time.
Um, he-- he won't be back.
The cops came.
Cops? What cops?
Anyone from the team?
Uh, no.
You sure?
- Anyone from the team show up there?
- No no.
- Yes or no!
- I'm saying no.
- No, nobody...
- Jesus Christ,
that little fucking weasel.
Larry, slow down.
Slow down, Larry!
- What now?
- Good evening, Mrs. McGorvey.
We were wondering
if Ronnie was home.
You leave him alone.
We just want a little
moment of his time. Just a little chat.
This is my house.
I pay the mortgage,
and I say who is
and isn't--
Yoo-hoo, Ronnie!
- Get your perverted ass down here now.
- I'm calling the police.
I hear they're well-disposed
to child molesters.
It's okay, Mommy.
Can I help you, gentlemen?
Ronnie, you go
on upstairs.
Larry, let him go. I think he gets
the point. We can go home now.
You listen to me, you
little piece of shit.
You stay the fuck away
from the town pool.
- You hear me?
- You're a bully!
My Ronnie would
never do what he did.
That poor child
at the mall--
what you did to him.
Larry?
Why did she
say that?
Oh, don't pretend you
don't know about me.
Everybody knows.
Everybody!
Look, h-honestly,
I-- I don't know anything.
I remember hearing
something...
a few years ago
when we first moved here, but--
something about
a-- a shooting
at the mall.
That's-- that's it.
That's all.
I didn't even
know you then.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Dispatch said there
was a shooter loose at the mall.
It was 10 minutes
from the end of my shift.
10 minutes and there would have
been someone else.
I can still see that
boy's face staring up at me.
Yeah, but--
but it was an accident.
You were trying
to stop a guy,
and the-- the boy
g-got caught
in the crossfire,
right?
No, I panicked.
There was no shooter.
Just the boy.
Antoine Harris
was his name.
He was big for his age,
only 13 years old.
He was a good kid.
Thought it was a joke,
waving around an air gun
at his friend
in the Big 5.
They were acting out some scene
from some movie they liked.
Shop girl saw it
from across the way,
called 911.
Jesus, that's terrible.
That...
well, you didn't know.
It could have
been real.
But it wasn't.
His parents...
uh, his parents--
I had to...
I was diagnosed with post-traumatic
stress syndrome
by three different
psychiatrists.
That's why I retired.
I couldn't do
the job anymore.
- So why don't you do something else?
- Like what?
Drive a forklift
at Costco?
Maybe you could
go back to school.
I loved my job.
I don't wanna do
anything else.
You ever think about the term
"homeland security"?
I mean,
really think about it?
The day that
you found out
that your father had
been killed in Iraq,
do you remember
that day?
Can you talk
about that?
You feel comfortable
talking about that?
After the men came
to tell my mom,
I cried,
but she didn't.
She just went up
to her room
and grabbed the pillows
off the bed,
cut the tops off of them
with a pair scissors.
There were feathers
all over the place.
That must have really
frightened you.
No, she was trying
to find the crown.
The crown?
The crown you leave
in your pillow
when you've slept on it
for a long time.
My--
my father had
two crowns.
Stop there.
- You hungry?
- No.
Mind if I get
some lunch?
No, go ahead.
Brad?
Honey, you there?
Pick up.
I know you're there.
It's Aaron's nap time.
Okay, I guess you guys
are out somewhere.
Um...
I love you both.
Bye.
I certainly did.
Here we go.
I don't know, Jean.
I don't think I'm up for this.
Well, now don't
be silly.
- It'll be fun.
- Really?
You're not the only
little sister here tonight.
- Oh, that's good.
- Oh!
Hi, would you
like a glass?
Did anybody like this book?
Because I really just hated it.
It's so depressing.
She cheats on her husband
with two different guys,
wastes all his money,
then kills herself with rat poison?
Do I really need
to read this?
Well, there is a lot
of good descriptive writing.
It's supposed
to be depressing.
It's a tragedy.
Madame Bovary was undone
by a tragic flaw.
What's her flaw?
Blindness.
She didn't see
that the men were
just using her.
She just wants
a little romance in her life.
- You can't blame her for that.
- It's about women's choices.
Back then, a woman
didn't have a lot of choices.
You could be a nun
or a wife.
- That's all there was.
- Or a prostitute.
She had a choice.
She had a choice not
to cheat on her husband.
I found it refreshing
to read about a woman
reclaiming her sexuality.
Is that a nice way
of saying she's a slut?
Madame Bovary's
not a slut.
She's one of the great
characters in Western literature.
I was a little puzzled
by some of the sexual references.
Look,
like this one.
Um...
"He abandoned
every last shred
of restraint
and consideration.
He turned her
into something compliant,
something corrupt."
Does anyone know
what that means?
It means
she's a slut.
Is he tying her up
or something?
Anal sex.
Mm-hmm.
Did everyone get that
but me?
Let's set that aside
for now.
I'm really eager
to hear what
our other little sister
has to say.
I'm not sure if you know this,
but Sarah has a Ph.D
in English lit.
Just a masters.
I never wrote
my dissertation.
Well, you still have
a lot more expertise
than the rest of us.
I think I understand
your feelings about this book.
I used to have some
problems with it myself.
When I read it
in grad school,
Madame Bovary just
seemed like a fool.
She marries
the wrong man,
makes one foolish mistake
after another.
But when I read it this time,
I just fell in love with her.
She's trapped.
She has a choice. She can either
accept a life of misery
or she can struggle
against it.
And she chooses
to struggle.
Some struggle--
hop into bed
with every guy
who says hello.
Well, she fails in the end, but there's
something beautiful
and even heroic
in her rebellion.
My professors would
kill me for even thinking this,
but...
in her own
strange way,
Emma Bovary
is a feminist.
Oh, that's nice.
So now cheating on your husband
makes you a feminist?
No no no.
It's not the cheating.
It's the hunger.
The hunger
for an alternative,
and the refusal to accept
a life of unhappiness.
Maybe I didn't
understand the book.
She just looks
so pathetic.
Is she pretty?
Who?
Your wife.
Degrading yourself
for nothing.
It's a simple question.
She's pretty, okay?
Do we have to talk about this now?
I mean, did she really think a man like
that was gonna run away with her?
Possibly.
How pretty is she?
A knockout.
Beauty's overrated,
Sarah.
Brad had meant this
to be comforting.
But at 3:00 in the morning, it had
precisely the opposite effect.
He had a beautiful wife,
a knockout, and she was sleeping
beside him right now.
Only someone who took
his own beauty for granted
would have been able
to say something so stupid
and with a straight face.
Weekends were difficult
for Sarah.
48-hour prison stretches
separating one happy blur
of weekdays
from the rest.
I'm going to the ocean.
- You are?
- I'm going to the ocean.
Is he doing
his ocean dance?
Sarah sometimes let herself
be carried away by fantasies
of a future very different from the life
she was living now,
in which she and Brad were
free to love each other
in broad daylight;
where they had no one
to answer to
but each other.
It could happen,
she thought. It had to,
because she wasn't sure she
could keep living like this
for very much longer.
Open your mouth again.
No, I don't want to.
May your mouth
be open.
May your mouth.
This is coming
into your mouth.
Open your mouth,
little fishy.
Hungry, hungry.
Little fishy
is not hungry?
You okay?
Yeah, fine.
- How about you?
- Great.
So how was
your weekend?
You really wanna know?
It sucked.
How was yours?
Terrible.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we went to the beach
and all Kathy and I did
was argue
the whole time.
Oh, you did?
Yeah, it was our
annual argument
over taking
the bar exam,
like our whole life
depends on it.
Get it over with.
You'll feel better.
It's this whole thing.
Gotta take a train
on Wednesday.
It's a two-day ordeal.
I'm not even
gonna pass.
- You'll be fine.
- No.
No, I won't.
I haven't cracked
a book all summer.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Don't-- don't do it.
- What?
- The test.
- Oh.
- Blow it off.
We should go somewhere,
just for a night,
you know?
Richard's out
of town till Friday,
and I'm sure I can get
a sitter for Lucy.
No, I can't do that.
I gotta take the test.
That's good.
- Looks good?
- Yeah.
Well, I have a good
feeling about this whole thing.
In fact, I think I'm gonna go buy
a bottle of champagne
and put it in the fridge,
and we can open it to celebrate
when we get
the good news.
Don't get your hopes up.
We've been
through this before.
Huh-uh. This time's
gonna be different.
I can feel it.
Can you believe it?
This is our first date.
Like a date, you know,
without the kids, I mean.
How was Lucy?
Did she cry or anything?
No, are you kidding?
With Jean there, she
just about shoved me out the door.
I thought we could make something
really beautiful.
I have so
many things here.
We could make...
a picture frame.
Or a jewelry box.
Or a hat.
Something for my mommy.
Okay.
- Stop it, stop it.
- No, Ronnie.
Ron-- Ron-- Ronnie,
just hold on.
Now there.
You look handsome.
She won't be disappointed.
Wait'll she hears
about my criminal record.
I don't think you need
to get into that just yet.
Why don't you stick
to small talk?
What if someone
recognizes me?
That's highly unlikely.
I made the dinner reservation
at a restaurant over
in Haverhill.
Sheila.
- Sheila.
- Yeah.
Something wrong
with the food?
No, it's fine.
Back at the house you
mentioned you were on medication.
- What kind?
- All kinds.
Mostly psychotropic.
So you had some kind
of a breakdown?
Mm-hmm, my junior year
in college.
You were that young?
What happened?
I don't really know.
Well, nervous breakdowns
don't just come out of nowhere.
Something must have
caused it.
I guess.
But I was fine before
I left for college.
I don't know.
Maybe it was the stress
of being on my own.
Maybe it's a chemical
imbalance in my brain.
Every psychiatrist I go to
has a different opinion.
This one guy, Dr. Faris,
he said I must have been
sexually abused as a child.
When I told him
I wasn't,
he said I must be
repressing the memory.
Right, um, so what
happened after that?
Did you drop out
of school?
Not right away.
My mother wanted me
to go
to the campus
counseling center.
And they wanted
the problem fixed, like I could just
snap my fingers and everything
would be okay again.
Yeah, I know
all about that.
You do?
Yes, I do.
So they said
I could leave school
and get married and have lots of kids
like my sisters,
and I can't take care
of kids.
I can't even take care
of myself
most of the time.
Besides, who's gonna marry me?
You're not so bad.
What?
You're--
you're not so bad.
I haven't had
a real boyfriend in six years,
not since my second
breakdown.
I had this thing happen
on a Greyhound bus.
- I was--
- Do you want me to wrap that up?
Oh, no, thank you.
No, wrap it up, please.
I'll take it home.
Folks gonna want dessert?
What do you say, Sheila?
You wanna share something sweet?
Let's make a little stop.
Take the next left.
Turn off the lights.
I had
a nice time tonight.
The last guy
I went out with,
you know what he did?
He ditched me.
He got up to go
to the men's room,
never came back.
Stuck me with the check.
Never said goodbye.
Never called
to apologize.
He wasn't my type anyway.
He was a big-shot CPA.
Super normal guy.
Didn't want to be dating some psycho.
But you seem like
a nice person.
Better not tell on me.
You hear me?
You better not tell,
or I'll fucking get you.
Hold on, Mom.
Hold on, Dad.
You should park the car
on the escalator, and back...
- So?
- What?
- Up, down and then up.
- Test, dummy. How'd it go?
It was all right.
You didn't call home
last night.
I was worried.
Go on the escalator.
Guess I could really use
that cellphone.
Go on the escalator.
- Well, look who's back.
- Oh, hi.
Hi, Jean.
Thanks.
You're a lifesaver.
So how was
your old roommate?
Oh, great.
Yeah, thanks for doing this
on such short notice.
Let me give you something
for your time.
That's not necessary.
No, really.
I insist.
Please don't.
Okay.
Uh, any calls?
Nope,
it was very quiet.
She's asleep on your bed.
It was a very busy day.
That's great.
Um, Jean,
is everything okay?
Yeah, she's
a wonderful child.
Mommy.
Mommy!
Yeah.
Are you coming?
- I have something.
- What?
I have something
for you.
Just give me
a second here, okay?
Brad.
Hmm.
Aaron's been telling me
about his new friend Lucy.
She sounds like
a sweet little girl.
What's her mother like?
Nice enough, I guess.
I can't even
remember her name.
Isn't it Sarah?
Sarah?
Yeah, Sarah,
from the pool.
Her daughter's name
is Lucy.
Oh, Lucy's mom.
Yeah, I forgot. That's right.
Her name is Sarah.
Hmm.
Yeah, it might be
really nice for Aaron
if they came over
for dinner.
Okay.
So you're
in advertising?
No, that's-- that's
a common misconception.
I'm not in advertising.
I'm in branding.
And that's very different.
Richard's pretty high up
in the company.
Yeah yeah,
I have these clients
and they'll come to me
when they have,
you know, a new product
they wanna sell.
Like, um, these guys,
they were in a couple weeks ago.
They're trying to open this chain
of Chinese restaurants, right?
They're talking to me
and I-- I look down at the table
and I realize that none
of these guys were Chinese.
Where were they from?
They're a bunch of fat cats
from Tennessee.
They think they can start a chain
of Chinese restaurants good enough
to fool the average
American boob.
Oh, God.
Mmm!
- This is delicious.
- Isn't it?
Brad's a fantastic cook.
So you guys see these
fliers with the guy's face
plastered all over
our village?
Lots of Sturm und Drang
in our quiet little town, huh?
Yeah, it's crazy.
What I want to know is why they let
a creep like that out of prison.
Some of the people
going after him are just as crazy.
- What do you mean?
- Well, just today I heard that
some nut's been spray-painting
the poor guy's house,
lighting fires on his porch.
God knows what else.
- Do they know who's doing it?
- Huh-uh.
They think
it's some ex-cop.
You know, that guy
who killed that kid at the mall.
Yeah, I don't think
it's him.
You're biased.
You're friends with the guy.
Brad's on that Committee
of Concerned Parents
with him.
I didn't know
you were on that.
I play on his
football team.
He asked me to distribute
some fliers.
He's on your team.
You never told me that.
Yeah.
You know what's weird?
I've never even seen this McGorvey guy.
- We did.
- No, we didn't.
Not you.
Me and Brad.
That day at the pool,
remember?
Yeah, I-I
totally forgot.
- Well, what happened?
- Sexual tension is an elusive thing,
but Kathy had
pretty good radar for it.
It was like someone had
turned a knob a hair to the right,
and the radio station
clicked in so loud and clear
it almost
knocked her over.
Once she became aware
of the connection between them,
it seemed impossible that
she'd missed it before.
On a hunch,
Kathy dropped her fork
in the hopes that
while retrieving it
she would catch Sarah
and Brad playing footsie,
- but she was mistaken.
- Asked him to leave, and he left.
But you know what?
He didn't look scary, right? I mean--
No, it-- it wasn't that big
of a deal, you know.
- No, he's like a regular guy, you know?
- Yeah, I mean--
Kathy, are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
Just a sec.
Brad had convinced
himself
the dinner party
had gone well.
That he and Sarah had managed
to put Kathy's suspicions to rest,
at least temporarily.
She certainly hadn't
accused him of anything,
or behaved in a way
that made him think
she'd noticed
anything untoward.
I'm really glad
they came over.
- Good night.
Two days later, however,
his mother-in-law showed up
for a surprise visit...
- Thank you, John.
- ...of ominously indeterminate length.
And from that moment on,
she accompanied Brad
and Aaron everywhere:
To the playground;
- We need some butter.
- To the supermarket;
And to the town pool.
Hi, Aaron.
Hi, Lucy.
The worst of it
was the pool.
Nevertheless,
after threatening all week
to go the football game,
Brad's mother-in-law decided against it
at the last minute.
- So are you coming?
- Well, I'd like to,
but I'm a little tired.
You sure?
You're welcome to.
No, go ahead.
You and Aaron
sure kept me hopping
this afternoon.
Looks like
you're on your own.
Oh, that's my ride.
- What time are you gonna be home?
- I don't know.
Pretty late, though.
Be careful and stay
out of trouble.
Winds whisper
of high hopes,
victory is in the skies.
One joins with many
on the summer's green field.
At 0 and 5, the Guardians
were the basement dwellers
of the Tri-County
Touch Football Night League.
The Controllers, a team of young
hotshots from the financial district
were 4 and 1
with an explosive offense
that regularly racked up
40 to 50 points a game.
But from
the opening kickoff,
this ragtag group
of law enforcement officers
decided to crunch
their own numbers.
But the Controllers
scored first
after recovering
a Bart Williams fumble
deep in Guardians' territory near
the end of the second quarter.
The Guardians evened things up early
in the second half...
moving methodically
downfield
on an 80-yard
touchdown drive.
The Controllers regained the lead
with a fourth quarter field goal.
With less than a minute
to go, trailing by three,
the Guardians faced
the extinction of their hopes.
- Down!
- It was their last chance--
4th and 5
on their own 35.
Set!
Hut, hut!
Yeah yeah yeah!
Yeah yeah!
Yeah!
Oh my God!
Brad, Brad!
What do you want?
Everyone is waiting for us at the bar.
Are-- are-- are you coming?
Why don't you go on ahead?
I'll catch up later.
You're gonna come, right?
I mean, we gotta celebrate.
Yeah yeah yeah,
I'll be there.
- You promise?
- Jesus, Larry, I just told you.
- Well, you got a ride?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I'll have a cold one
waiting for you.
Larry, you have
to go home now.
Just give me five more minutes.
He promised he was coming.
I don't care what he promised,
I want to lock up.
Now get your butt
out of here!
Now!
When I looked up there
and saw you it was just...
wow... wow.
Thank God you came.
I don't want
to go home.
I want to stay
right here forever.
No, I do.
For the first time in my life
I feel like anything is possible.
Like I can do anything, you know?
What are we doing?
What do you mean?
It's not real, Brad.
What?
This. It's wrong
and it's weird.
How long are we
gonna sneak around together?
How long can that last?
I can't do this anymore.
No, no don't
say that.
As long as I know that
we're gonna have this--
Have what?
What is this?
Look...
if that dinner at your house
was any indication,
you seem pretty happy
with your wife.
You know, you have
a perfect life
- and I don't wanna to be the--
- Okay, stop stop stop.
Run away with me.
What?
You don't mean that.
You believe in me.
Come on.
We'll go away,
figure this thing out.
It's not weird.
The kids are comfortable
with each other.
I know there's more
to it than that, but...
let's do this.
Please.
Please, Sarah.
Oh my God.
You really mean
it, don't you?
Yes.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Yes!
Okay, yes.
Fucking Brad, I'm so
sick of hearing about Brad.
I'm fucking over it.
I don't even like him.
He's a loser.
"Brad made
the fucking touchdown."
Yeah, you know why
he hasn't the balls to show up here?
'Cause I fucking made the block.
It's bullshit.
That's why he's not even here,
he's fucking embarrassed to see me.
I don't even like anybody
in this fucking town.
Wake up, wake up!
Wake up, Woodward Court!
Okay, I'm awake.
Open your eyes! Get your goddamn heads
out of the sand!
My heads?
My goddamn heads?
Don't you people
love your children?
Don't you want
to protect them from evil?
Woodward Court,
there's a pervert in your midst!
There's a goddamn
pervert in your midst!
Open your eyes!
Protect the children!
Save the children!
Wake up
and see the grass!
- Just stay inside, Ronnie.
- Save the children!
Open your goddamn eyes!
Wake up and save
your children!
You dirty son of a bitch!
Get off my lawn!
Who the hell do you think you are,
Mr. High and Mighty?
No perverts
in Woodward Court!
You think you're God?
Far from it!
I don't think I'm God!
I never said I was!
You murderer, you
killed the boy.
I didn't murder anyone. Now why don't
you go back inside, put some clothes on?
You shot him through the neck.
I read it in the paper.
- No perverts in--
- You son of a bitch. Give me that.
Hey hey!
Give me that!
You're--
- You need to go home.
- The police are coming.
I mean, you're
scaring my kids.
Your kids need
to be frightened!
They live across
the street from a pervert!
Ow! Oh!
Oh my God, Mrs. McGorvey.
Are you okay?
May. May!
May-- I think we should
call an ambulance.
Karen, call an
ambulance, right now!
- I'm doing it!
- Oh, fuck.
- May!
- This is all I need.
Excuse me, Mr. McGorvey,
we need to ask you some questions.
$14.35.
The Fed continuing its
campaign against inflation
by raising short-term interest rates
for the 10th time yesterday.
Usually there is a correlation between
inflation and gold prices.
Let's take you over
to our stocks desk...
Cafe con leche?
Thank you.
Kim Bryson, please call
the operator.
Madre.
Me too.
She's resting.
Get down, knock it off!
Quiet.
Bring him around.
It's all yours.
Mr. McGorvey.
I'm afraid we
have some bad news.
Do you have a mortuary
to make arrangements for you?
It's not a problem. The hospital has
a list that I can provide you with.
Here's what's
going to happen:
Your mother's body
will remain in her bed
for up to three hours.
Three hours is typical.
But if there's a request for more time,
depending on our occupancy,
that's usually
not a problem.
If there's anyone
you need to call--
family, friends--
they're welcome to full
bedside visitation privileges
before the body is taken
downstairs
to be prepped
for transport.
Do you have any questions
that come to mind?
Anything I can
help you with?
- No.
- Okay.
I'd like to remind you to take your
mother's personal belongings with you
before you leave
the hospital today.
And all I need from you now
is to sign this release-
of-remains form.
Aaron.
Hey hey, buddy.
Can you wake up?
Could you take your
hat off for me?
Just for a second.
Are you mad
at me, Daddy?
No.
No no no, not at all.
I just want you to know
that I love you very much,
and I would never do
anything to hurt you, okay?
Okay.
Now you can go
back to sleep.
Lucy, come on.
Let's go.
I will not go
in the car seat!
- You have to go in the car--
- I will not go in the car seat!
Yes, you will!
- You will go in the car seat.
- No, I won't!
Yes, you will.
Go in the car seat.
I will not go
in the car seat!
Okay, just...
you don't have to
go in the car seat.
You can just go here.
No, actually...
go on the floor.
Okay.
Okay, go down on the floor.
You have to stay down, okay?
Mommy is gonna get arrested.
Just stay down, okay?
Okay.
Mommy, I want to go home.
Yeah, in a minute,
as soon as Brad gets here.
Hello?
Ronnie?
Oh my God.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah! Let's do it. Let's go!
Hey, dude!
What's the hurry?
Yeah! Oh!
- This is so sick.
- Damn.
- Nice.
- Oh, man.
Yeah, man.
- How about you take a run?
- What?
Yeah, give it a shot.
See what happens.
You guys are crazy,
I can't do that.
It's not about that,
it's about skating.
Whoo!
Come on.
Do you need help?
She's g-- gone.
She's gone.
Who?
Who's gone?
Mommy.
Mommy's gone.
I...
I'm sorry.
She loved me.
She's the only one.
Mommy died.
Lucy?
Lucy! Lucy!
Lucy!
Get in the car seat!
It's okay, Mommy.
Lucy.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Would you like
to go home?
Yeah?
Brad.
Brad, can you hear me?
D-- don't move.
The ambulance is on its way.
Jesus.
What happened to me?
These kids say you've been
out cold for the last five minutes.
- You almost had it.
- Dude, you were awesome.
- That shit was gnarly, son.
- Back up, back up! Give him some space.
You just hold still, all right?
Hold still.
Hey, bro!
Here, this fell
out of your pocket.
I don't need it anymore.
- Hey, Duane.
- Hm?
Could you call my wife?
You got it, buddy.
Here we go.
I'm so sorry, Ronnie.
I really am.
I never wanted anything
like this to happen.
Are-- are you--
are you okay?
- Oh, no!
- Gonna be good now.
Oh my God!
Hold on, Ronnie.
You hold on.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
You hold on there,
okay, buddy?
In his wildest dreams
Larry would never have imagined
he'd once again be in this position,
where precious
minutes count.
Tonight he could
save a life.
He knew Ronnie had done
some bad things in the past,
but so had Larry.
You couldn't
change the past.
But the future could
be a different story.
And it had
to start somewhere.